if you have a collection of objects that
have five different possible
characteristics you need a proper five-
set vend diagram like this one notice in
this diagram there are 32 possible
regions created by the five sets there
are five regions shown here that lie in
exactly one set after that we see 10
distinct regions pictured here that lie
in exactly two of the sets by symmetry
there are also 10 regions as shown here
that lie in exactly three of the sets
the five regions shown here lie in
exactly four sets and finally we have
one region that lies in all five sets
and one region that lies outside of all
five sets so this is a beautiful proper
five set vend diagram can you draw one
with six sets